To each their own, but personally, I think Miyamura looks best with long hair.
They're making a sequel! Part two of that horror flick I love is in the works!
Whoa, really?
I felt drawn to him as a fellow bespectacled classmate, since our numbers are few.
And his long hair gave him an air of mystery.
It was sensational.
Watabe! Did you find that reference book I asked for, or...?
I say we go see it on opening day.
Uh, sure, it's a date. Yay.
That said, this fun-loving Miyamura's nice, too.
I approve.
Yo! Watch Step-Up Pick a Miyamura!
To memorialize him?
Now I have even more questions.
Share this video.
See ya.
Our friend, the
Thank you.
Horty's the huge horror buff, not me.
Bet the pair of you would be friends at first fright, huh?
Uh, well, it's hard to say.
But, uh, I still enjoy it even though I'm not a fanatic.
Oh, you do?
That's so great!
It means we share a hobby now.
Yeah.
It's like I can feel the hearts floating off his sleeves and into my personal space.
Oh, common interests are so fun.
Here, check these other books out, Miyamura.
Okay.
Hey, everybody.
You're just in time for a special treat.
How does a steaming cup of chow and mushy sound?
Goodbye, yours truly, so you know it still is.
Ah, thanks, Kiyosuke.
But what makes this one special is the ginkgo nuts.
And it was my idea to add them in the first place.
Oh, that was a good call.
Like father, like son.
Huh?
Hey, I was wondering when you...
Stop!
Did I stink?
Of Watabe funk.
Normally, there's a trace of Toru or Shindo.
This is cursing my wimp, I've been.
I can't breathe.
While I'm choking on that stench.
How you know what Watabe smells like is the real question.
I took samples in case the scenario played out.
What scenario?
You can smell people's scent on me even if we just talk?
Female scents do not compute.
The only ones that do are male.
And now you're a robot?
I don't smell a thing.
You don't have to detect any strange aromas.
What counts as I can?
But I kind of want to.
So I'll be able to tell if you've been with someone else.
Be it hanging out or...
I see.
What you really want is a means to determine if I surround myself with guys all day the same way that you do.
That phrasing irked me a little bit.
But yeah, basically.
Well, I don't.
Um, we both know that's a lie.
I can think of two.
You always hang around with Ishikawa and the Prez.
But I'd never know that just by getting a good whiff of you.
How about we make a deal then?
If I cheat, I'll tell you to your face.
That'd be a big help.
Thought so.
Dude is ready!
She went ballistic.
I'm talking vain, popping mad.
Like, I've never been the best at studying, so I have no clue why.
But I guess I could buckle down and really apply myself, huh?
Worth a try.
It could be a whole lot worse, Ishikawa.
If I so much as play a CD, the cord gets yanked out.
No tunes.
Music helps stimulate the brain, though, doesn't it?
All of their expectations are sky high.
Can't they see we're doing our best down here?
The heck?
I can't tell.
Yeah.
How much you want to bet it's hoodie-related?
Two, no, three million.
They're just weirdos.
It's the core of who they are.
What's up?
I hardly ever get invited to your place.
Though I always love it when I do.
Oh, but you can hang on to that controller.
I have more at home.
That's not the reason I asked you to come over.
And even if you want it, you can't have it.
Then what's the deal, dude?
I...
I want you to close your eyes.
Huh?
Are you going to do something to me?
Yeah.
No way.
It'll be over quick.
What, Will?
You can end so many things in a moment.
Including my life!
Then explain if I thought you'd get it.
Just close your eyes.
What for?
What are you going to do once you rob me of my life, Miyamura?
Fine!
You can look, but shut up and sit still!
There.
If anyone made a move, it'd be you.
But I have your scent memorized now.
Time out.
Who am I making moves on?
Shut up!
I'm going to ask you anyway, because no one else will.
Are you listening?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Once I save these babies in my Miyamura folder, I'll be all ears.
I hear your camera snapping pictures like there's no tomorrow.
Do you have a folder just for Miyamura?
A sketch?
But yeah, so my hesitant question.
Are you crushing on Miyamura?
It goes far beyond that level of attachment.
I find him greatly fascinating.
I can't explain it.
But there's Hori, his ever-charming girl.
I don't follow.
You speak as if that's a bad thing?
Miyamura dating the opposite sex is moe.
If you're a fan, then you're aware he has guy friends from other schools, yeah?
You know, like Shindo?
There are boys outside of the school he has affection for.
Creepy.
No, he's a pal, not a creep.
Don't think of pals as creeps.
Okay, so you just admire him from afar?
I'd love to touch him one day.
Oh, wow.
Okay, let me rephrase that.
Like, do you ever want to talk to the guy?
I don't have that desire since I recorded him.
What's up, Watabe?
I am extremely concerned.
Hey!
Come play some ping-pong!
Ishikawa, if an asteroid that was two kilometers in width
crashed into me at this very moment,
I'd die a happy soul.
No regrets.
A space rock that size would kill Miyamura on Impact 2, you know.
Eureak!
Watabe, bitch!
It fellin' all over you!
Now, for some reason, it's much stronger today.
He thinks he's marking his territory.
He's gonna rephrase!
You're saying I smell worse than usual?
I didn't even notice him get that close.
There are also hints of Shindo and Tanihara on you,
but Watabe's stink overpowers them both.
And why wouldn't it?
His odor is as intense as his interest in you,
an obsession that puts the other boys in your life to shame.
How can you know all that from someone's B.O.?
I'm telling you, despite what your nose detects,
I didn't lay a finger on that kid.
Doesn't matter how many fingers came into contact with him.
You're scent is the only one I would know anywhere.
You'd think that'd also be true for girls like Yoshikawa or Ayasaki.
I thought you'd finally do it.
Huh?
The way you whipped around.
I thought you were gonna manhandle me into next week!
Quit getting my hopes up, you T's!
I can't believe they were high enough to make you cry when they fell!
I'm sorry!
You dummy!
Don't you dare touch me now!
Enough with the deodorizer spray!
Traffic accident?
No.
It was man-made.
Howdy, huh?
Oh, boy.
So you two fought again?
Mm-hmm.
I don't know who won, but she got you good.
I don't care what she says or does.
I'm not apologizing this time around.
Morning.
Hori, what happened to your face?
Ugh, that must hurt.
Dude, did you hit her back?
No, no!
You are such a dummy, I swear!
Go on!
If you've got something to say, by all means, say it!
Nah, I'm set.
If you're just gonna have a dumb tantrum, though, then I'll leave, dummy.
That's rich!
The dummy's calling me dumb?
Man, you piss me off so much!
But...
Got so worked up, she smacked right into the doorframe.
Hard.
Ugh...
Okay, but what sparked this fight?
I forgot like I always do.
This time, though, I won't budge until Hori says she's sorry!
How manly.
Yeah, good luck.
The sheer nerve of this guy!
It didn't face him!
Not one bit!
Miyamura's such a dummy!
There, there.
Don't cry.
It's fine.
There isn't even another woman involved, so why are you getting this upset about it?
Guys are just as dangerous.
I forgot you hit your head.
Get well soon, okay?
Wake up and tune in!
Just dump the guy.
No!
Why should I?
Look, I'll put it to you this way.
What do you do when you push him too far, and Miyamoto stops caring about you romantically or otherwise?
Nothing's guaranteed.
Even somebody you share a past with can always choose to leave.
When Sengoku says it, I want to punch him.
But when Kono says it, I suddenly see the light.
Yeah.
Thanks, Kono.
Hey.
I'm still angry as hell.
This might take a minute.
Time to submit our group's opinion, ladies and gentlemen.
You know what?
I'll just make it my opinion.
Go right ahead.
Who cares if you answered at the same time?
Damn.
I'm more worn out than the combatants.
I'm sorry you got involved, man.
Oh, but why am I angry?
Huh.
My brain's so exhausted I can't remember now.
If you're serious, this is going to go in an endless loop of spite.
Just kiss and make up already.
I really would like to.
Oh.
No touch.
I see you've chosen death.
Nabs and paper towels.
Ew, you smell.
Look at that, I'll confuse you.
What am I doing?
Jeez.
It's my fault.
So just say sorry and end it.
Stop being stupid.
Hey, Miyamura.
Have you seen Hori?
Why?
She was absent from that last class.
Huh?
I went and checked the nurse's office and the girl's locker room.
But no dice.
You went in the girl's locker room?
Well, I'm getting kind of worried about her now.
I'm worried you went in.
Wherever she went, she left her bag.
Hope she's not out in that cold.
Yeah.
Wait.
Outside?
There she is.
What?
Hmm?
Oh, um, nothing.
So it's over, right?
You stopped caring about me.
Huh?
Just because we have a past doesn't mean we have a future.
Uh.
I imagine you already hate me.
Why, Hori?
Why?
Well, because...
Uh, you're crying?
Seriously?
Come on, now.
There's nothing to cry about.
But I...
I constantly get irritated.
And then I take it out on you.
It's so unfair.
Who knew she knew?
I want to look at you.
Just move your hands.
Please.
There.
Aw, you're really crying a river.
Prove that even monsters need a good cry.
Your ears and nose turned crimson red, too.
Falling like a baby in the middle of school?
That's tragic.
Shut your face!
How...
How are you always so freaking nice?
Makes me think about dumb stuff like what I do if you started hating me!
Is that really what got you this worked up?
Jeez, Hori.
I swear.
Though you named me the reigning dummy king,
the crown suits you just as well.
I know I'm the queen to your king, okay?
But you're still dumb or by a mile!
You're surprisingly self-aware.
Granted, there is one thing you haven't realized.
And that's how very hard I've fallen for you.
Hating you would be difficult.
Dummy Morda strikes again!
With the words in the eyes!
But I was being honest.
My bad.
Sorry, I like you.
Dammit.
That wasn't at fault, but I apologized anyway.
I'm sorry.
Yeah!
Duh!
You didn't do anything wrong, got that?
I'm at fault a hundred out of a hundred times, all right?
All right.
Context would death help if I had it,
but from up here,
that sure looked like a direct kick to the gut to me.
It did.
Scary.
Good morning.
Hey.
Morning, Miyamura.
A hoodie?
So, that look is a choice.
You shouldn't have been the one making it, though, for real.
That's not quite your style.
It looks warm, though.
Gee, thanks.
Wow, this is a first.
Guess so.
I wore this since my normal clothes were in the wash.
Ah.
Sometimes it's nice to spice it up.
You really think?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, friendos!
Someone lend me their Japanese book!
Oh, whoa, Miyamura!
Is that a hoodie?
Trying to jack my style?
Negatory.
She's not, but gay matching!
I struggle to get this look to catch on each year
when the cold has had its worst,
but it never, ever does!
Well, it is against the dress code.
You're looking a little too sharp, though, Miyamura,
so why not add some flair to show it off, yeah?
Uh, okay.
He's violating the dress code,
and you want him to flaunt it?
Oh, that's lit!
Put those shades back in the student council room, show!
Put your fingers more like this.
Dope, d-dope.
Enough!
Take your modern Japanese textbook
and go bother your own class!
Now I'm gonna wonder why Shu's so big on hoodies
for the rest of the day.
Maybe they're like the ultimate item that he can equip.
Whereas my stats probably take a hit
while I'm wearing a hoodie.
Seems I gotta channel Iyuda, I guess,
to rock this look.
No.
Do not make Iyuda your finish line.
Strive to be like anybody except him.
Poor Iyuda.
Ha!
So it's true!
You are breaking dress code!
Morning, Mr. President.
Good morning!
I ran into Iyuda in the hall just now.
He was thrilled to tell me you've adopted his style.
More like I'm borrowing it for the day.
Did you tell off Iyuda for his hoodie?
Don't play faves.
He's a lost cause.
I don't waste my breath on him,
so no.
Poor Iyuda.
Yes, lunchtime!
Hey, the school got a new flavor of hot tea today.
You see it?
Not yet.
What is it?
One you'll like, I'm sure.
To the tea!
Hold up, Miyamura.
Hmm?
Your hut's rumbled.
Oh, is it?
Thank you.
If you're gonna break school rules,
make it look good.
Huh?
Ah!
Jeez!
What prompted you to do that?
Curiosity?
Because that could be...
Let's hurry!
I can't fool Hori.
What you think?
Gonna wear it again?
Nah, tomorrow it's back to my cardigan.
Stare.
Miyamura!
You coming over?
Nope!
I need a head home today.
See you later!
Do not tell me they had another fight.
Okay.
Hey, good morning, Hori.
Great morning.
This warm weather rocks.
Yeah.
Very sunny.
You're warm enough to ditch your scarf.
Stare.
Hmm?
What's wrong?
Come here a sec.
I'm getting kind of anxious about this.
What are you...
Yay!
You smell like yourself again!
Huh?
That's, uh...
Awesome!
I should have known that's what she was up to.
Miyamura, you have a wonderfully unique smell.
I was surprised when I couldn't pick it up from that white hoodie.
Stare...
Um...
Cause it's Shindo's.
He left it at my apartment the last time he stayed over.
I knew it.
I ran it through the wash, so how did your nose know?
Because it was obvious to me.
Well, that makes one of us.
I mean, your scent is my favorite smell in the entire world, Miyamura.
Make sure that you return Shindo's hoodie, okay?
Huh?
Uh...
You're cold!
Let's go.
Uh...
Yeah, let's...
Just gonna leave it at that?
Oh!
Good morning!
Uh-oh!
What's up?
Nothing but the sky.
And it's a beautiful day.
Then, I bought this much more, too.
I bought a lot of things that I bought for you.
I also got a lot of things that I bought for you.
Thank you.